jindalnaturecure.org 2012-01-26

# Untitled Page

Jindal Naturecure Institute - Privacy Policy   
\--------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------------- 

Jindalnaturecure.org respects your privacy. This Privacy Policy provides succinctly the manner your data is collected and used by Jindalnaturecure.org. You are advised to please read the Privacy Policy carefully. By accessing the services provided by Jindalnaturecure.org you agree to the collection and use of your data by Jindalnaturecure.org in the manner provided in this Privacy Policy. 

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should contact Jindalnaturecure.org at info@jindalnaturecure.org.

The Policy does not apply to the procedures and practices followed by entities that are not managed, owned or controlled by jindalnaturecure.org or to the people that are not engaged, employed or managed by jindalnaturecure.org 

**We want you to**

  * feel comfortable using our web sites 
  * feel secure submitting information to us 
  * contact us with your questions or concerns about privacy on this site 

**WHAT INFORMATION IS, OR MAY BE, COLLECTED FROM YOU?**

We will automatically receive and collect certain anonymous information in standard usage logs through our Web server: 

We may collect the following personally identifiable information about you: 

  * Personal information such as name including first and last name, date of birth (DOB) and other details  as mentioned in application form
  * email address 
  * mobile phone number and contact details 
  * demographic profile (like your age, gender, occupation, education, address); 
  * Personal health details as mentioned in application form. 
  * financial information (like credit card numbers);

**WHO COLLECTS THE INFORMATION?**

We will collect anonymous traffic information from you when you visit our site. 

We collect the personally identifiable information from you when you register with us. During registration you are required to give us your contact information (such as name, email address, gender, cell number). Upon registration, users may receive communications from jindalnaturecure.org.  Also we collect other information like DOB, occupation, marital status, age, height, weight, accommodation want, days you will stay, passport & visa details, personal health details etc.

We use this information only for our internal use. 

The Site does not contain link to any other web sites. Hence there is no chance to use your information by other website. 

We are the sole owners of your information collected by us at several different points on our Website. 

**POLICY UPDATES **

**We reserve the right to change or update this policy at any time by placing a prominent notice on our site. Such changes shall be effective immediately upon posting to this site. ill post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently.

You can offer your views, suggestions, if any, by submitting the filled in suggestion/feedback functionality available in our website. 

**
